<resources>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Your Second Label Here</string>
    <string name="first_fragment_label">Your Label Here</string>
    <string name="app_name">My Application</string>
    <string name="main_title">English Developer for\n State Exam</string>
    <string name="main_subtitle">Start preparing</string>
    <string name="title_activity_preparing_sections">PreparingSections</string>
    <string name="reading_section">Reading</string>
    <string name="listening_section">Listening</string>
    <string name="writing_section">Writing</string>
    <string name="grammar_section">Grammar</string>
    <string name="speaking_section">Speaking</string>
    <string name="Task_1">Task № 1</string>
    <string name="Task_2">Task № 2</string>
    <string name="Task_3">Task № 3</string>
    <string name="Check_answer">Проверить ответы</string>
    <string name="reading_task1">Установите соответствие между текстами A–G и заголовками 1–8. Занесите свои ответы в таблицу. Используйте каждую цифру только один раз. В задании один заголовок лишний.
     1. Crafty celebrations                    5. The birthday weekend
     2. Playing at a birthday                  6. A secret preparation
     3. Months for celebrations            7. Once-in-a-lifetime
     4. An old tradition                            8. Expressing greetings

    A.      A Golden Birthday is a special, unique event that occurs when a person turns the age similar to a birth date.
For example, a girl who celebrates her birthday on the 17th of June will have a golden birthday in the year she turns 17.
A person who is older than 31 years will have already passed the only golden birthday and will not have it again.
Many people miss their golden birthdays because it is not a wellknown celebration.

    B.      Humans tend to have babies throughout the year, rather than in certain seasons like other species. However, there are
certain months when more babies are born than usual. These birthday months can vary from country to country depending on
how close one is to the equator. In countries close to the equator November is the month with the most birthdays and those
furthest from the equator have the most birthdays in September.

    C.      Families can take a creative approach to birthday celebrations by letting guests make their own clothes or jewelry.
T-shirt projects are easy to adapt to any age group. Young children may enjoy finger painting to make
various designs on blank"T-shirt's, while teens and adults may prefer to use paint pens or fabric markers to produce
unique patterns. Adults and kids who are old enough to handle tiny objects can make nice jewelry.

    D.      There are many ways to surprise one's best friend for the birthday. Whether one chooses to give a wonderful gift
or throw a wild party, it is important to make the surprise a mystery. If one's best friend finds out about the surprise
before the right date and time, the shock element of the surprise is ruined. For the ideal execution of a surprise party,
a quick rehearsal with friends and family beforehand may also be necessary.

    E.      One of the easiest and most traditional ways to send a happy birthday message is to call, email
or send a postcard to the person. Some other methods include creating a photo gallery, sending flowers,
ordering a favourite song on the radio or setting up a gift treasure hunt. The message needs to be as personal
and unique as possible. It is always good to say something that expresses love and appreciation for that person.

    F.      The annual birthday celebration is generally marked by a cake with candles. The origin of birthday candles
is related to a Greek tribute to the moon goddess. Artemis. Candles were lit and placed on a cake as a tribute
to her beauty. Later, in Germany, children celebrated a birthday with a cake alight with one candle for each year of life,
plus one extra candle to represent the expectation of living another year.

    G.      Many classic games such as musical chairs, hot potato and Simon Says work well as birthday party entertainment.
Games should match the age, abilities and interests of the party guests. Bingo is simple enough to fit any party context
by filling the squares with related words or images. Pictures work best for young kids who can't read yet.
Pin the tail on the donkey is another game that is easy to adapt to various party themes.</string>

</resources>